Tyler McNiff

California, United States



tylermcguy@gmail.com



https://crazy-dev-hero.netlify.app/

Summary

Hi I have 6+ years of experience in Blockchain Development.

Fully familiar with several Blockchains like

- ✓ Ethereum, BSC, Avalanche, Polygon ...
- ✓ Solana, Terra ...

Crypto Payment Gateways | Tokenization | Defi | DEX | CEX | NFT Marketplace (minting/staking) | NFT Metaverse | Smart Contract Development & Audit | Cryptocurrency | Wallets.

Tech-stacks available:

- ✓ Solidity, Rust,
- ✓ Python, Golang, C++,
- √ Web3.js, Ethers.js
- ✓ React.js, Nodej.s, Next.js, Typescript, Express.js
- ✓ MySql, SQLite, PostgreSQL, MongoDB,

I have been a self-motivated Learner with extensive experience in Blockchain and Decentralization with modern technologies.

Experience



Blockchain Developer

MetaRents

Apr 2022 - Present (2 months +)

- MR Protocol Development and smart contracts audits
- Building a rental marketplace DApp

vo Blockchain Developer

Upwork

Dec 2021 - Present (6 months +)

THANKS TO PANDEMIC, pH7 cancelled some of their private projects and many of us got fired.

Again worked on Upwork as a freelancer - hooking new projects from different area/time-zones.

pH7 Technologies Inc.

Apr 2021 - Dec 2021 (9 months)

Worked as blockchain consultant, smart contract developer(EVM, Solana)

Senior Developer

Hidden Brains InfoTech Pvt. Ltd.

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020 (10 months)

- Management of software build, release and deployment process.
- Experience in developing websites and web applications and also good knowledge of Mac operating system.
- Well versed with scripting languages.
- Testing products to ensure that they work satisfactorily and also in controlled and real-life environments.
- Leading junior software developers.



Blockchain Expert

Privi

Jun 2016 - May 2019 (3 years)

- Audit the already created Defi smart contracts.
- Developed smart contracts for tranding ERC20 tokens.
- Developed one dex platform based on the Deri protocol(https://deri.finance).
- Integrated the Loan platform by using Compound protocol(https://compound.finance)
- Developed nft marketplace(smart contract | Web3 | centralized backend) involving sale | blocking | rental features.
- Attended to the Realm Metaverse project as a web3 engineer.

Education



Cornell University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Sep 2013 - May 2016 Ithaca, NY 14850

Skills

Blockchain • Smart Contracts • Solidity • Decentralized Applications (DApps) • Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) • Cryptocurrency • Metaverse • ethers.js • web3.js • Hardhat